http://therightcast.com/privacy-policy

TheRightCast.com
Online Acting Resources, casting notices, online headshots and resumes, e-postcards, and more.
What This Privacy Policy Covers
This privacy policy relates to use of the {TheRightCast.com} web site at http://www.therightcast.com/
This privacy policy covers how TheRightCast.com (hereafter named ‘we’) will treat personal information that we collect. Personal information is your information and includes identifiers like your name, address, email address, phone number.
We will not send you any junk emails. Furthermore we will not send you any information unless you have specifically requested we do so. An exception to this rule will be the initial email validation when you create a new account.
Children under 13 are not permitted to use the TheRightCast.com service, and so this privacy policy makes no provision for children’s use of the site.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
TheRightCast.com may update this policy at any time for any reason. If there are any significant changes to how we handle personal information we will send a notice to the primary email address specified in your TheRightCast.com account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.
If you have questions or suggestions you can contact us at: info@therightcast.com
Comments on this entry are closed.
Current Members Log In
User Name:
Password:
Search TheRightCast
Categories
Acting Information (1)
Agents (1)
Auditioning (3)
Finding Acting Work (2)
The Working Actor (23)
Recent Posts
Ten Little Rules for a Rockstar Theater Audition
Don’t Get an Agent!
Workshops Work if You Work It
A Star is Born in the Background – How to get Extra Work
Working the World Wide Web
Tag CloudActing Blog
acting scams
acting services
Acting Websites
actor office supplies
YouTube
Recent CommentsLaura Crowder on ACTING 123 by Linda StuartAmanda DePastino on A Star is Born in the Background – How to get Extra WorkWendy Alane Smith on Workshops Work if You Work Itjessica on Don’t Get an Agent!brianna Melvin on A Star is Born in the Background – How to get Extra WorkYolanda Fitts on A Star is Born in the Background – How to get Extra WorkSamuel F. Campbell on A Star is Born in the Background – How to get Extra Workpamela on 9 Tips For Audition Successesu ebeigbe on A Star is Born in the Background – How to get Extra WorkCassandra on 9 Tips For Audition Success
Copyright © 2020 TheRightCast.com
| Contact
| Advertise
| Terms Of Service
| Privacy Policy
For Actors:
For Casting Directors and Producers:
Casting Services
| Post A Casting Notice
For Talent Agents:
Talent Agent Services
Help
